flyupload.com 2009-12-18

# Upload & Share Files - Flyupload

  | 

Last Updated: May 6, 2007 

FlyUpload is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our users. This policy applies only to FlyUpload. Our privacy policy statement will help you understand FlyUpload's commitment to safeguarding your private information. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

FlyUpload does not collect any personal or individually identifiable information without the informed consent of the user. The only page where we collect personally identifiable information is on our .Contact Us. form. We use this information (such as name, email address) only to respond to your inquiries or feedback. You may not opt-out of receiving our response. We will not sell, share, or rent your confidential information to third parties, including individuals or other organizations. 

**INTELLIGENT CACHING**

FlyUpload may occasionally use caching technology to cache frequently requested Web content. Caching mechanisms are used to serve web pages directly from the FlyUpload local storage as a means to make web performance faster and more efficient. We do not cache or locally store any end-to-end web content transfers, like e-commerce transactions, via the Secure Socket Layer (SSL). 

**INTERNET COOKIES** FlyUpload may use a feature of your Internet browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer to maintain a session state. These short-lived cookies are not written to your hard drive and are removed when you close the browser. This means that not only are your web activities kept private, but also that your hard drive memory is not depleted. Our customizable user preferences feature uses a single cookie, which is stored on your local hard drive. This cookie is used for user customizable privacy options. FlyUpload does not, and will not, use cookies to retrieve personal information about you. 

We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate usage and volume statistics to help target advertisements to the user. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See Third Party Advertisers. 

**SHARING**

We may share aggregate demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information and cannot identify any individual person. 

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS**

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by third party ad servers. We share Web site usage information about users with our advertisers for the purpose of targeting our Internet advertisements on this site. 

Google Analytics, ValueClickMedia, Tribal Fusion, Google AdSense uses cookies and clear GIFs on this site, which allow it to recognize a user's cookie when a user visits this site. The information that Google Analytics, ValueClickMedia, Tribal Fusion, Google AdSense collects and shares through this technology is not personally identifiable. 

**LINKS**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that FlyUpload is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information for their protection. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the FlyUpload web site. Note that when you choose to use the remove ads feature on our site that you will be taken to PayPal's site and that their privacy policy governs the use and collection of the data submitted. We encourage you to review their privacy policy. 

**SERVER LOG FILES**

We use server logs to analyze trends, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for performance assessments and aggregate use. We do not log the sites that users visit. The logging data is collected as part of our attempt to monitor ongoing performance and service integrity in order to enhance our service offering. We have implemented strict technical and organizational measures to ensure that the log data is protected at all times and destroyed after statistical analysis by our security and performance engineering teams. Performance statistics logs are collected from time to time in order to evaluate the scalability of the FlyUpload service and/or introduce new service enhancements. Log files are not tied to personally identifiable information. 

**SECURITY DISCLOSURE**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [support@luckystar.me](mailto:support@luckystar.me). 

**LEGAL DISCLOSURE**

We reserve the right to disclose your collected information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

**CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: 

LUCKY STAR S.r.l.  
Via delle Ande  
00144 Rome  
Italy  
info@luckystar.me

|
